Register of the Germany Deutsche Kongress-Zentrale records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Personnel File, 1943 (Box 350-357)
  - Kauffman, Isabella
  - Kayer, Elfrieda A.
  - Kielblock, Gertrud
  - Kinat, Leo
  - Kirch, Fritz
  - Kirchner, Gertrud
  - Klapproth, Johannes
  - Kleffel, Hanni
  - Klein, Hilde
  - Kleiner, Leopold
  - Kleinschmidt, Margot
  - Klemann, Margarete
  - Klemon, Ursula
  - Kleophas, Gerhard
  - Klingeberger, Hans
  - Klipsten, Ursula J.
  - Knobloch, Klara
  - Knoll, H. E.
  - Knopp, Ortrud
  - Knothe, Herta
  - Koberne, Elisabeth
  - Koehnke, Klaus
  - Kolbenheyer, Klara
  - Komlienovic, Ivan
  - Konietzko, Bruno
  - Kopitzke, Erwin
  - Korb, Frida
  - Korndahl, Marie
  - Kost, Renate
  - Krafft, Karl E. (Box 355)
  - Kramer, Hermann Albert
  - Kratochwill, Rudolf
  - Kraus, Irene
  - Krause, Peter von
  - Krauss, Irmgard
  - Krichkauff, Gisela
  - Krisper, Franz
  - Kroeger, Brigitte
  - Kronshage, Frieda
  - Krueger, Hilde
  - Krumhaar, Herbert Ritter von
  - Krug, Alice
  - Kuehnscherf, Henriette
  - Kuehn-Bamberger, Wilhelm
  - Kuehn-Steinhausen, Hermione
  - Kuhlmann (first name unknown)
  - Kulawiez-Gajewska, Sylvia
  - Kuesel-Glogau, Hermann
  - Ladehoff, Otto
  - Lande, Heinz
  - Landauer, Albert
  - Landsberg, Anka
  - Lange, Otto
  - Lanwer, Gerhard
  - Lawory, Fritz
  - Lehmann, Gustav
  - Lehriger, Erna
  - Leiner, Adolf-Guenther
  - Leist, Hermann
  - Leser, Doris
  - Leser, Ingeborg
  - Liebold, Herta
  - Lienhard, Gerda
  - Lilienfeld, Constance von
  - Lilienthal, Agnes
  - Limburg-Stirum, Paula von
  - Linke, Rudolf
  - Lorey, Jakob
  - Lozinski, Lozina von
  - Luckau, Josef
  - Ludwig, Elfrieda
  - Luethke, Charlotte
  - Luppee, Clara
  - Mainka, Alfons
  - Martin, Grace Hellen
  - Martinovici, Alexandrina
  - Massenback, Konstantin Freiherr von
  - Mast, Herbert
  - Matejo, Josef von
  - Mazeck-Walter, Suzette
  - Mechlernov, Marko
  - Medem, Ellen von
  - Medem, Manfred von
  - Melbrich, Alexander
  - Mennong, Anny
  - Merensky, Jutta
  - Mergert, Rieckhof
  - Meyer, Alma
  - Meyer, Anna
  - Meyer, Hermann H. (Box 356)
  - Milbradt, Gertrud
  - Milbradt, Helene
  - Mittelsteadt, Edeltraut
  - Moebus, Amelia
  - Morenhaven, Josef
  - Morze, Ingeborg voni
  - Motz, Charlotte
  - Mueller, Else
  - Muller, Hans
  - Mueller, Liesel
  - Muennich, Ricardo
  - Mundler, Anneliese
  - Muser, Hermann
  - Naso, Dietrich von
  - Naumann, Marlene
  - Nehrkorn, Almut
  - Neumayer, Lilla
  - Neuwohner, Otto
  - Nielsen, Reiner
  - Nowakowski, Georg
  - Oertzen, Etta von
  - Offe, Klaus-Heinz
  - Oppenlaender, Ruth
  - Ormonde, Erna
  - Otto, Sigrid
  - Pagel, H.
  - Pahn, Ursula
  - Pardatscher, Hermann
  - Patschke, Margarethe
  - Paul, Guenter
  - Paulovsky, Louis H.
  - Petschigg, Lilli
  - Peyke, Hans
  - Pfeiffer, Adele
  - Pfeiffer, Karl
  - Pfeiffer, Otto
  - Pflever, Carl
  - Pfluck-Hartung, Elfriede von
  - Pla, Jose
  - Plaumann, Jose
  - Plotho, Olga von
  - Pomarici, Marie
  - Pomtreff, Ann-Marie
  - Pommer, Valentin
  - Popp-Koehler, Estella
  - Poretschkin, E.
  - Post, Kaethe
  - Quadfasel, Hanna
  - Reihnert, Rudolf
  - Rhode, Emmy
  - Rieckhof, Margarete
  - Rietschle, Heinz
  - Riz, Franca
  - Rueffert, Gertrud
  - Sande, Albert von der (Box 357)
  - Schaefer, Fritz
  - Schmoll, Lou
  - Schulz, Gustav
  - Sforza, Finocchidi
  - Smyser-Kund, Helga
  - Snijders, Hermann Johan
  - Soltek, Wilhelm
  - Somac-Sidjakowa, Lydia
  - Thuedener, Alfred
  - Tillmann, Rudolff
  - Tonkovick, Josef
  - Trautschold, Carl
  - Ulle, Else
  - Veugel, Paul
  - Voelter, Frida
  - Voss, Alfred
  - Voss, Marie-Elise
  - Walter, Marie
  - Wanek, Ditta
  - Weber-Tkaczuk, Hans
  - Wennholz, Erich
  - Werkmann, Martha
  - Wichers, Hans-Georg
  - Wildner, Margarete
  - Witte, Marianne
  - Zahn, Grete
  - Zerbes, Georg
- Miscellaneous Clippings, 1880-1943 (Box 358-379)
  - Geographical file (countries) (Box 358)
    - Afrika, 1939
    - Arabien, 1949
    - Australien, 1938
    - Belgien, 1917
    - Bulgarien, 1942
    - Bulgarich-Jugoslavien, 1941
    - China, 1938
    - Daenemark, 1941
    - Deutsch-Bulgarisch, 1941-1943
    - Deutsch-Daenisch, 1941
    - Deutsch-Englisch, 1938
    - Deutsch-Finnisch, 1942
    - Deutsch-Franzoesisch, undated
    - Deutsch-Indisch, 1942
    - Deutsch-Italienisch, 1940-1942 (Box 359)
    - Deutsch-Japanisch, 1941-1942
    - Deutsch-Niederlaendischu, 1941-1942
    - Deutsch-Schwedisch, undated
    - Deutsch-Slowakisch, 1941
    - Deutsch-Spanisch, 1941
    - Deutsch-Ungarisch, 1941-1942
    - Englisch-Russisch, 1921
    - Finnisch-Deutsch, 1941
    - Finnland, 1941-1942
    - Frankreich, 1941-1942
    - Griechenland, 1942
    - Grossbritannien, 1942 (Box 360)
    - Grossdeutschland, 1940-1941
    - Indien, 1942
    - Italien, 1942
    - Italienisch-Deutsch, 1942
    - Italienisch-Kroatisch, 1941
    - Japan, 1941
    - Mandschukuo, undated
    - Niederlande, 1941
    - Norwegisch-Deutsch, 1941
    - Portugal, undated
    - Portugiesisch-Spanisch, 1942
    - Rumaenien, 1942
    - Rumaenisch-Spanisch, 1942
    - Schweden, 1941
    - Schweiz, 1941 (Box 361)
    - Serbien, undated
    - Skandienavien, 1941
    - Slowakei, 1941
    - Spanien, 1942
    - Spanisch-Amerikanisch, 1942
    - Spanisch-Deutsch, 1941
    - Sudamerika-Argentinien, 1940
    - Sudamerika-Peru, 1940
    - Tuerkei, 1935
    - UdSSR, 1942
    - United States of America, 1940 (Box 362)
  - Cities
    - Berlin (Germany. Deutsche Kongress-Zentrale), 1936
    - Frankfurt am Main, 1942
    - Muenchen, 1942
    - Paris, 1942
    - Salzburg, 1942
    - Wien, 1942-1943
    - Zuerich, 1942
  - Unprocessed clippings (Box 363-374, 379)
  - Realkatalog der DKZscopecontent (Box 375-378)
    - 1-3 (Box 375)
    - 4-5 (Box 376)
    - 5-6 (Box 377)
    - 7-10 (Box 378)
- Personnel Card File (Box 380-426)
  - Outline of a handbook of international organizations provided for publication by the DKZ (Box 380)
  - Card files (Box 381-383)
    - Printed quotations on different issues provided by professional quotations services (Weltkartei der Wirtschaftspresse, Politischer Zitatendienst) (Box 381-383)
    - Devisenantrage (in alphabetical order of persons and institutions that applied for foreign exchange) (Box 384)
      - Old card files
        - Ma (Box 385)
        - La (Box 386)
        - Lu (Box 387-388)
        - See New card files (Box 389)
        - Wi (Box 390)
        - Thy (Box 391)
        - Sch (Box 392)
        - Ga (Box 393)
        - Gr (Box 394)
        - Gl (Box 395)
        - Lu (Box 396)
        - Ma (Box 397)
        - Hu (Box 398)
        - Pa (Box 399)
        - Ru (Box 400)
      - New card files (Box 389-425)
        - Bi (Box 389)
        - Ib (Box 401)
        - NSDAP (Box 402)
        - Op (Box 403)
        - Pi (Box 404)
        - In (Box 405)
        - Sa (Box 406)
        - Sp (Box 407)
        - Schm (Box 408)
        - Ze (Box 409)
        - Wi (Box 410)
        - We (Box 411-412)
        - Soh (Box 413)
        - St (Box 414-415)
        - Br (Box 418)
        - De (Box 419)
        - Ei (Box 420)
        - Fi (Box 421)
        - Gr (Box 422)
        - Ha (Box 423)
        - Z (Box 424)
        - Ho (Box 425)
- Musterkollektionen der DKZ (3 binders) (Box 426-428)
- Bibliographical Card Files (Box 429-430)
- Incremental Materials (Box 431-447)